<LUMSOMSADHomePageData>
    <Faculty description="This module manages department's faculty profile and maintains their academic activities. Faculty members' profile can be added and updated as required. Faculty research grants and publications can be added dynamically to their portfolio. MS and PhD students supervised and courses taught by a faculty can also be maintained. The module provides a detailed reporting mechanism with an excellent support of run time CV and faculty scholarly report generation in pdf.">
        <Faculty>This section is related to faculty members. In this section we can add or update basic information, education, contact information, honors, awards, fellowships, job experiences, collaborations, research interests, biography and services of faculty members. Reports about publications, research grants, courses and supervisions can be generated. Faculty member can be assigned courses to be taught in a semester.</Faculty>
        <Research_Grants>This section deals with research grants of faculty members.  Basic information of research grant can be add or updated. One can assign principal investigator, co-principal investigators and collaborators from the system. We can add team of the research grant from existing students of the university.</Research_Grants>
        <Books>This section deals with book publication. We can add or update book detail, authors, photos, and publisher name of the book. We can view all the books and can also delete any book. Book information can be imported from external file.</Books>
        <Book_Chapters>This section deals with book chapter publication. We can add or update chapter details, authors, photos, and book details of the book. We can view all the book chapters and can also delete any chapter. Chapters can be imported from external file.</Book_Chapters>
        <Journal_Papers>This section deals with journal publications. We can add or update journal details, authors and photos of the journals. We can view all the journals and can also delete any journal. Journals can be imported from external file.</Journal_Papers>
        <Conference_Papers>This section deals with conference publications. We can add or update conference details, authors and photos of the conference. We can view all the conference papers and can also delete any conference paper. Conference papers can be imported from external file.</Conference_Papers>
        <Workshop_Papers>This section deals with workshop publications. We can add or update paper details, authors, photos, and workshop details of work shop. We can view all the workshop papers and can also delete any workshop paper. Workshop papers can be imported from external file.</Workshop_Papers>
        <Technical_Reports>This section deals with technical reports . We can add or update paper details, authors, photos, and technical report details of technical report. We can view all the technical reports and can also delete any technical report. Technical reports can be imported from external file.</Technical_Reports>
        <Scholarly_Report>This sections deals with scholarly reports.  Scholarly reports of any faculty members are generated yearly. One can export the report on external PDF file. Scholarly report includes faculty courses, publications, research grants, project supervisions, thesis supervisions, PhD supervision.</Scholarly_Report>
        <Configurations>Configurations can be added and updated manually. We can add or update the configuration for designation, departments, conference ranks and faculty statuses.</Configurations>
    </Faculty>
    <Students description="This section of the website is related to student affairs. In this section, the record of students can be created, maintained, viewed and updated as required. Currently MS and PhD students of the SSE are catered for. Along with that, the record of courses and semesters are also maintained here. Students can also be enrolled in courses, theses, independent studies, projects.">
        <Students>students</Students>
        <Courses>courses</Courses>
        <Semesters>semesters</Semesters>
        <Configurations>configurations</Configurations>
    </Students>
    <Inventory description="This section of the website is related to inventory and room affairs. In this section, the record of inventories and rooms can be created, maintained, viewed and updated as required. Currently Allocation and De-allocation of inventories are catered for. Along with that, Map association for room are also maintained here. Rooms can also be associated with map location, independent of locations.">
        <Inventory>In inventory section along add update and delete functionality, Allocation and De-allocation facility of inventories provided. Reports can be generated for inventory allocation, Inventory history, Inventory type and Inventory status.</Inventory>
        <Room>In room section along add update and delete functionality, Room association with a location on map, facility is provided. Reports can be generated for room allocation, room history and room type.</Room>
    </Inventory>
    <Staff description="This section of the website is related to Staff affairs. In this section, the record for Administrative staff, Undergraduate students, Teaching Assistant and Research assistant can be created, maintained, viewed and updated as required. Along with that, Teaching Assistant and undergraduate students take courses history can be maintained here. ">
        <External_Research_Assistant>Information for a research assistant can be created, maintained, viewed and updated as required. Along this Association of a research grant and respective faculty member, facility is provided.</External_Research_Assistant>
        <External_Teaching_Assistant>Information for teaching assistant can be created, maintained, viewed and updated as required. Along this Association of a teaching assistant with courses and semester, facility is provided.</External_Teaching_Assistant>
        <Undergraduate_Student>Information for undergraduate student can be created, maintained, viewed and updated as required. Along this Association of a undergraduate student with courses and semester, facility is provided.</Undergraduate_Student>
        <Administrative_Staff>Information for a staff member can be created, maintained, viewed and updated as required.</Administrative_Staff>
    </Staff>
</LUMSOMSADHomePageData>